Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Other, 1956-1980 (bulk 1970s)
  - 32 B-14, Florida Power and Light Contracts, New York Power Pool Operating Policy, 1977, April 4 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-15, Florida Power and Light Contracts, PJM Interconnection Operating Instructions, 1970-1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 C-1 EPRI Contract, 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - 32 C-1 EPRI Contract, 1978-1980, 18 folders (Box 46)
- Human Factors Series, 1979-1981
  Contains reports, correspondence, schedules, and printed materials concerning human safety factors in nuclear reactors and electric power dispatch control centers, and human errors and limits in control in the nuclear utility industry. Comments are made by the Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers (IEEE) and the Atomic Industrial Forum (AIF). Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 33-12 IEEE on Human Factors in Nuclear Safety, 1979 Dec. 2-7 (Box 46)
  - 33-14 Human Factors Workshop Papers, 1979 (Box 46)
  - 33-15 AIF Comments of Nuclear Reactor Committee on NUREG-0659, 1981 May11 (Box 46)
  - 33-16 Human Factors Review of Electric Power Dispatch Control Centers, 1981 July (Box 46)
- Chernobyl Series, 1970-1989 and undated (bulk 1980s)
  The Chernobyl Series contains materials on the nuclear plant accident of April 26, 1986. Reported to be the worst nuclear disaster in history, the plant in the USSR exploded thereby releasing radiation into the air. This accident caused the United States to take an indepth look at its own nuclear facilities. Roddis collected information on this incident and headed a group that investigated the "N"(Nuclear)-Reactor in Hartford, Washington (same type of plant as in Chernobyl) to see if it was safe. Consists of correspondence, Department of Energy (DOE) memorandums, transcripts of congressional hearings, articles, press releases, reports, photographs, clippings, and briefings on the accident at Chernobyl. Also contains reports, articles, correspondence, and notes from meetings concerning general nuclear safety, public fears of nuclear power, nuclear reactors design, the nature of hydrogen in nuclear plants, nuclear safety in Russia, and effects of the incident on Russia's economy. Two reports found in this series include the The Accident of Chernobyl and its Consequences by the USSR State Committee on Utilization of Atomic Energy and 'N'-Reactor Updated Safety Analysis Report compiled by Roddis's research group. See also AIF series.
  - Soviet Nuclear Power Attempts a Comeback Following Chernobyl, 1980 Apr. 27 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence Regarding "N" Final Report, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
  - Louis H. Roddis, Jr. Final Report "N", 1986, Oct. 3 (Box 46)
  - Chernobyl "N" Drafts, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Louis H. Roddis, Jr. "N" Report Drafts Copies, 1986 Oct. (Box 46)
  - "N" Reports (Others), 1986 (Box 46)
  - Chernobyl Articles, 1987 (Box 46)
  - "N" Reactor Briefing, 1974-1986 (Box 46)
  - "N" Joint Appendix, 1986 (Box 46)
  - "N" at Savannah River Site, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
  - Chernobyl/"N" Press, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
  - Bad Test Blew Up Chernobyl Reactor Article, 1986, July 25 (Box 46)
  - Energy Content Comparisons, 1986 June-July (Box 46)
  - "N", 1986 Aug.-Sept. (Box 46)
  - Department Organization, 1980-1986 (Box 46)
  - Department of Energy Trip, 1986, July (Box 46)
  - "N" Reactor Choice Items, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Advisory Committee on Reactor Safeguards (ACRS)/"N" Reactor, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Washington, D.C. Visit Regarding the "N" Reactor, 1986 June 20 (Box 46)
  - General Design Study, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC)/Northwest Power Pool, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Hanford Administration And Agenda, 1986 (Box 46)
  - DOE News Releases; Office of the Secretary Letters, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Los Alamos National Lavoratory (LANL) Agenda, 1986 (Box 47)
  - Chernobyl Choice Items, 1986, 2 folders (Box 47)
  - "N". Reactor Visit to Washington, D.C., 1986-1987, 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Effects, 1986 May (Box 47)
  - Chernobyl--A Special Paid Report, 1986 May 8 (Box 47)
  - "N" Reactor Design, 1972-1986 (Box 47)
  - RBMK Design, 1986 Apr.-May (Box 47)
  - Articles on Accident, 1986 (Box 47)
  - USSR Chernobyl Accident Press Coverage, 1986 (Box 47)
  - "N" Reactor Press Releases and News Clips, 1986 May-July (Box 47)
  - Soviet Power Reactors, 1974 and 1986 (Box 47)
  - Reports on Effects of Chernobyl Accident on Nuclear Power Development, 1986 (Box 47)
  - Various Press Releases, 1986 Apr.-May (Box 47)
  - Letter from John S. Herrington, 1986 Nov. 13 (Box 47)
  - "N" Reactor Design Review Team, 1986 Sept. (Box 47)
  - Special Team Report, 1986 Sept. (Box 47)
  - Technical Safety Appraisal Team, 1986-1990 (Box 47)
  - RBMK Descriptions, 1980-1986 (Box 47)
  - Fuel Elements of the RBMK-1000 Reactor, 1977 Oct. (Box 47)
  - Physical and Power Startup of the First Unit of the V.I. Lenin Nuclear Power Station in Leningrad, 1974 Aug. (Box 47)
  - Development of Uranium-Graphite Channel Reactors in the USSR, 1977 Nov. (Box 47)
  - Radioactive Safety Barriers in Nuclear Power Stations, 1974 Jul. (Box 47)
  - Recent Developments in Hydrogen Technology Vol. 2, undated (Box 47)
  - A Critical Review of Recent Large-Scale Experiments on Hydrogen-Air Detonations, 1986 Feb. 7 (Box 47)
  - Descriptions of Selected Accidents That Have Occured at Nuclear Reactor Facilities, 1980 Apr. (Box 47)
  - Stability of the Radial and Azimuthal Energy, 1978 Nov. (Box 47)
  - Light Water Reactor Hydrogen Manual, 1983 Aug. (Box 47)
  - HECTR Version 1.0 User's Manual, 1985 Feb.6 (Box 47)
  - Mathematical and Experimental Study of Emergency Cooling of RBMK 1500 Reactor in Case of Maximum Credible Accident, 1982 Sept. 8 (Box 47)
  - Construciton Parameter for Chernobylskaya Atomnyye Elektricheskiye Stantsii (AES) Given, 1985 Mar. 12 (Box 47)
  - Zirealoy-Oxidation and Hydrogen Generation Rates in Degraded Core Accident Situations, undated (Box 47)
  - A Safety Assessment of Department of Energy Nuclear Reactors, 1981 Feb.-Mar. (Box 47)
  - Steam Carbon Reactions, 1986 May 5 (Box 47)
  - Intex, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Design of the RBMK-1000 Reactor, 1977 Feb. (Box 47)
  - The Channel Type Nuclear Power Reactor, 1980 (Box 47)
  - Design of the Reactor Unit, 1980 (Box 47)
  - Refueling Machine, 1980 (Box 47)
  - Means of Control, 1980 (Box 47)
  - Study of Safety Problems, 1980 (Box 47)
  - Graphite-Water, Steam-Generating Reactor in the USSR, 1981 Oct. (Box 47)
  - Nuclear Power and the Scientific-Technical Systems in Development, 1978 Mar. (Box 47)
  - Some Characteristics of and Experience with the Operation of Nuclear Power Plants with RBMK-1000 Reactors, 1983 Apr. (Box 47)
  - Experience in the Construction of Large Power Reactors in the USSR, 1976 Feb. (Box 47)
  - Construction of Nuclear Power Plants, 1983 May 7 (Box 47)
  - Safety Aspects of Large-Scale Combustion of Hydrogen, 1986 Jul. 20-24 (Box 47)
  - Safety of Power Plants with Boiling-Water Graphite Channel Reactors, 1977 Dec. (Box 47)
  - Soviet Atomic Energy, 1979 Sept. (Box 47)
  - Design Provision for Operational Capability of a Nuclear Power Plant with a High-Powered Water-Cooled Channel Reactor in Emergency Regimes, 1981 Apr. (Box 47)
  - Soviet Nuclear Power Program, undated (Box 47)
  - U.S. Reactor Safety, 1986 Apr. 29 (Box 47)
  - Directory of Nuclear Power Plants in the World, 1985 (Box 47)
  - General Safety Regulations of Nuclear Power Plants During Design, Construction, and Operation, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Safety Analysis Reviews for the Department of Energy's Defense Facilities Can Be Improved Report, 1986 June (Box 47)
  - Glennan Report, 1982 Nov. 15 and undated (Box 48)
  - Deadly Meltdown, 1986 May 12 (Box 48)
  - Removal of Iodine and Particles by Sprays in the Containment Systems Experiment, 1971 Apr. (Box 48)
  - The Institut De Protection et de Surete Nucleaire (IPSN) Report on the Chernobyl Accident, 1986 June. (Box 48)
  - Unloading Surplus Absorbers from the RBMK-1000 Core, 1985 Sept. 13 (Box 48)
  - Effectiveness of Emergency Cooling of Water-Cooled Power Reactors, 1983 (Box 48)
  - Measurements of Spectral Indices in Uniform RBMK Reactor Lattices for Various Channel to Graphite Temperature Gradients, 1981 Mar. (Box 48)
  - Operating Efficiency of Steam Separators in Power Plants with RBMK Reactors, 1982 Aug. (Box 48)
  - Chernobyl Skaya AES Third Phase Construction Begins Article, 1984 Jan. (Box 48)
  - Possible Criterion for Additional Safety Requirements for Nuclear Stations Sited Near Large Cities, 1981 July (Box 48)
  - Nuclear Safety Regulations for Nuclear Electric Power Plants, 1977 Jun. 15 (Box 48)
  - State of the Art and Development Prospects for Nuclear Power Stations Containing RBMK Reactors, 1984 June (Box 48)
  - Hydrogen Behavior and Control at Light Water Reactors, undated (Box 48)
  - Visit to Leningrad Power Station, 1978 Feb. 11 (Box 48)
- Particulars of Startup and Adjustment on the Third Generating Unit of Chernobyl AES, undated
  - N-Reactors, 1978 and undated (Box 48)
  - The Leningrad AES TMENT V.I. Lenin, 1980 Apr. (Box 48)
  - Hydrogen Transport in Containments, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Contractor Safety and Fire Protection Conference, 1958 Jun. 24-25 (Box 48)
  - Emergency Localization System at Third Unit of Chernobyl AES, 1984 Jan. (Box 48)
  - Accident at the Chernobyl Plant, 1986 Jun. (Box 48)
  - The Russian Graphite Moderated Channel Tube Reactor, 1976 Mar. (Box 48)
  - Nuclear Graphite, undated (Box 48)
  - N Reactor Updated Safety Analysis Report (NUSAR):
    - Volume 1, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 1, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 2, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 2, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 3, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 3, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 4, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 4, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 48)
    - Volume 5, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 49)
    - Volume 5, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 49)
    - Volume 6, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 49)
    - Volume 6, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 49)
    - Volume 7, Part 1, 1978 (volume) (Box 49)
    - Volume 7, Part 2, 1978 (volume) (Box 49)
  - Tests on Improved Steam Separators in the Third Unit at the Chernobyl Nuclear Power Station, 1984 Dec. (Box 49)
  - Problems of Nuclear Science, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Nuclear Energy, Man, and the Environment, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Degree of Perfection of Graphite and Changes in its Properties under Irradiation, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Ways of Altering the Coefficients of Reactivity in RBMK Reactors, 1979 Jun. (Box 49)
  - Emergency Cooling Heat Transfer Problem of Nuclear Reactors, undated (Box 49)
  - The Metal-Water Reactions of Irradiated N-Reactor Fuels at 1025 to 1080 Degrees Celcius, 1970 Aug. (Box 49)
  - Survey of Neutron Physics Investigations on the RBMK-1000 Reactor, 1977 Feb. (Box 49)
  - Physical Characteristics of an RBMK Reactor in the Trransitional Period, 1982 Dec. (Box 49)
  - Basic Approaches to Nuclear Power Safety in the U.S.S.R., 1977 Nov. (Box 49)
  - Conference on the Fifth Anniversary of the Commissioning of Lenningrad Nuclear Power Station, 1979 May. (Box 49)
  - Safety Under Servicing Cooling Conditions for RBMK Reactors, 1984 Aug. (Box 49)
  - An Experimental Study of Emergency Cooling Conditions in RBMK Reactor on Load Disconnection, 1984 Aug. (Box 49)
  - Experimental Study of Emergency Cooling Modes, 1984 Aug. (Box 49)
  - Analysis of Russian Fuel Bundle Hydrodynamics and Heat Transfer Based on Available Data., 1986 June-July (Box 49)
  - USSR State Committee on the Utilization of Atomic Energy--The Acccident at Chernobyl and its Consequences, 1986 Aug., 2 folders (Box 49)
  - The Accident at Chernobyl AES and its Consequences (Alternate Translation), 1986 Aug. 17, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Press Reports, 1986 Apr.-May (Box 49)
  - Seminar on Operating Procedures for Abnormal Conditions in Nuclear Power Plants, 1986 Jun. 23-27 (Box 49)
  - Accident Localization System of Energy Units with RBMK-1000 Reactor, 1984 Feb. (Box 49)
  - Post-Meeting Accident Review Slides, undated (Box 49)
  - Performance Monitoring Management Information, 1986 May (Box 49)
  - Performance Objectives and Criteria for Technical Safety Appraisals, 1986 May, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Progress Report Chernobylskaya AES 4th Power Block, 1984 Dec. (Box 49)
  - Experience in 10 Years of Operating Channel-Type Nuclear Reactors Recounted, 1983 Dec. (Box 50)
  - Thermal Expansion of Structural Graphite and the Effect of Neutron Irradiation, 1979 Nov. (Box 50)
  - Nuclear Power Generating Units with RBMK-1000 Reators Described and Evaluated, 1979 (Box 50)
  - Operation and Maintenance of Nuclear Powerlants, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Study of Operating Conditions of Power Generating Unit with RBMK Reactor with False Turning on of Reactor's Emergency Cooling Sysytem, 1984 Mar. (Box 50)
  - Performance of Leningrad Nuclear Electric Power Station Reviewed, 1981 Aug. (Box 50)
  - Small Light Water Graphite Reactor Preconceptual Design Report --Plant Description, 1985 Dec., 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Chernobyl in Perspective, 1987 Jun. (Box 50)
  - Various Articles Sent from Hal Lewis, 1948-1986 (Box 50)
  - Additional Articles about RBMK Reactors, 1986 Jun. 4 (Box 50)
  - Examination of AES Safety Regulations, 1984 (Box 50)
  - Various Articles, 1984-1986 (Box 50)
  - Documents from Russian Literature, 1977-1986 (Box 50)
  - N Reactor Safety Oversight Technical Issues Briefings, 1986 Jul.(volume) (Box 50)
  - N Reactor Safety Oversight, 1986 Jun. (volume) (Box 50)
  - Additional Unusual Occurence Information, 1986 Jul. 25 (Box 50)
  - Technical Aspects of Hydrogen Control and Combustion in Severe Light-Water Reactor Accidents, 19871989, 1 folder (Box 50)
  - N Reactor Carbon 14 Sources and Inventory, 1986 Jun. 24 (Box 50)
  - Summary of Reported Field Office Assistance Efforts Related to Chernobyl, 1986 May (Box 50)
  - Environmental Monitoring at Hanford, 1984-1985 (Box 50)
  - Procedures for Conducting Safety Appraisals, 1986 Mar. 14 (Box 50)
  - Report to the American Physical Society of the Study Group on Radionuclide Release from Severe Accidents at Nuclear Power Plants, 1985 July (Box 50)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1986 Jun. 16 and Aug. 5 (Box 50)
  - DOE Responsibility, 1980-1986 (Box 50)
  - Stored Energy Analysis, 1986 June (Box 50)
  - Oregon Governors Report, 1986 Aug. (Box 50)
  - Department of Energy to Congress--Energy Plans, 1986 (Box 50)
  - Chernobyl Reports by Central Electricity Generating Board (CEGB), Stone and Webster Engineering Corporation (S&W), International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA), and RKS Sweden (Nuclear Safety Board of the Sweedish Utilities), 1986 and undated (Box 50)
  - Canadien Deuterium Natural Uranium Reacto (CANDU) Fuel (like N Reactor), 1967-1972 (Box 50)
  - Articles on Aftermath of Chernobyl, 1989-1991 (Box 50)
  - Safety Issues at the Defense Production Reactors, 1987 (Box 50)
  - Soviet Reactor Incident Briefing Book, 1986, 1 folder (Box 50)
  - Soviet Reactor Incident Briefing Book, 1986, 1 folder (Box 51)
  - Safety Issues at the Test and Research Reactors, 1988 (Box 51)
  - "N" Reactor Accelerated Safety Enhancement Program Vol. 5, undated (Box 51)
  - "N" Reactor Reviews Comment Resolution Plan, 1987 Mar. (Box 51)
  - Ford Briefing, 1987 May-Oct. (Box 51)
  - "N" Reactor Safety Enhancement Program, 1987, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Information on Pressure Tube Rupture Analysis, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 51)
  - Conference on Nuclear Risks, 1986-1987 (Box 51)
  - The Chernobyl Cover Up, 1989 Nov. 13 (Box 51)
  - Various Magazine Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 51)
  - USSR-VVER Summary, 1981-1986 (Box 51)
  - VVER Reports, 1981-1986 and undated (Box 51)
  - Medium-Sized Plants; Atom Energo Export Imatran Voima Oy (AEE-IVO) Finland, 1981-1986 and undated (Box 51)
  - VVER Tech Papers--USSR, 1983-1986 (Box 51)
  - Soviet Nuclear Power Plants, 1986 (Box 51)
  - USSR Hydrogen Safety, undated (Box 51)
  - Design of Basic Equipment--VVER, 1986 Mar. 7 (Box 52)
  - VVER Finland, 1980-1983 and undated (Box 52)
  - VVER's USSR Extracts, 1986 Jan. 13 (Box 52)
  - Operating Modes; VVER and USSR, 1982 Jan. 7 (Box 52)
  - VVER Bulgaria, 1977-1987 (Box 52)
  - House of Representatives Presentation, 1987 Oct. 28 (Box 52)
  - Senate Hearings, 1987 Mar. 12 and Nov. 13 (Box 52)
  - Senate Hearing, 1987 Jul. 17 (Box 52)
  - Senate Hearing--Other Witnesses, 1987 Jul. 17 (Box 52)
  - Indexes, 1986 Jun. and undated (Box 52)
  - Chernobyl Briefing, 1986 May (Box 52)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory Correspondence, 1974-1986 (Box 52)
  - Administrative Items, 1986-1988 (Box 52)
  - Hearings on the "N" Reactor, 1985-1987 (Box 52)
  - Hydrogen, 1982-1986 (Box 52)
  - Savannah River Press, 1988 (Box 52)
  - "N" Reactor Press, 1987-1988 (Box 52)
  - Legasov Memoir, 1988 June (Box 52)
  - Chernobyl--Later Press Clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 52)
  - Chernobyl--One Year After Press, 1986-1987 (Box 52)
  - Chernobyl--Early Press Clippings, 1986 (Box 52)
  - Control of the Environmental Consequences of the Release of Radioactive Materials, 1987 Apr. 25 (Box 52)
- Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority, 1979-1984 and undated
  The Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority (PREPA) is a federally controlled company that runs the production of electric power in Puerto Rico. Roddis worked in connection with the Blue Ribbon Panel which evaluated the activities of PREPA. This series provides insight to the creation, purpose, and activities of PREPA. Contains committee meeting minutes, correspondence, photographs, schedules, notes, and reports on PREPA including a report from the Blue Ribbon Panel evaluating PREPA and PREPA's response to the report. Topics include recommendations for better efficiency and lower costs, and look at the feasibility of producing Puerto Rico's energy from coal.
  - Coal Water Slurries are Ready for Utility Boilers Report, 1984 Dec. (Box 52)
  - Notes on San Juan Meetings, 1983 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 52)
  - PREPA Coal, 1983 (Box 52)
  - Financial Impact of Investment in A New Coal-Fired Generating Plant, 1983 Apr. (Box 52)
  - Executive Summary, 1983 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence with Rafael Luis, 1983 May 6 (Box 52)
  - Power Revenue Bonds--Series H, 1982 Dec. 1 (Box 52)
  - Fuels Office Monthly Reports, 1982 Dec.-1983 Apr. (Box 52)
  - Center for Energy and Environment Research at the University of Puerto Rico Annual Report, 1982 (Box 52)
  - Fuels Office Monthly Reports, 1983 Feb. and May (Box 52)
  - Balliro Correspondence, 1983 (Box 52)
  - Balliro Correspondence, 1983 Apr. (Box 52)
  - Balliro Correspondence, 1983 Feb. 23 (Box 52)
  - Fourth National Energy Plan, 1983 (Box 52)
  - PREPA Coal Water Slurries, 1983 (Box 52)
  - San Miguel Correspondence, 1983 Mar. 15 (Box 52)
  - Puerto Rico Business Review, 1983 Mar. (Box 52)
  - PREPA Coal Conversion, 1982-1983 (Box 52)
  - July Weekly Generation Reports and April Monthly Production Division Report, 1983 (Box 52)
  - Fuels Office Monthly Reports, 1983 Jun.-Sept. (Box 53)
  - Weekly Generation Reports, 1983, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Production Division Monthly Report, 1983 Mar. (Box 53)
  - Report of the Blue Ribbon Panel, 1983 (Box 53)
  - Evaluation of the Aguirre Station Project Proposal by Atlantic Export Corporation, 1982 Dec. (Box 53)
  - The Evaluation of the Economic Feasibility of Conversion to Coal-Fired Generation at Aguirre, 1982 May (Box 53)
  - Exhibits of Revised Computer Runs, 1982 Aug.2 (Box 53)
  - Coal Conversion Report--Phase 2 Study, 1981 Oct. (Box 53)
  - Report on Coal Conversion Alternatives at Aguirre Steam Plant, 1981 Oct. 26 (Box 53)
  - Aguirre Station Units 1 and 2 Coal Conversion Report--Phase 1 Study, 1981 Sept. (Box 53)
  - Preliminary Investigation--Conversion to Coal; Units 1 and 2, 1981 Jul. (Box 53)
  - Investigations for the Dredging of Two Proposed Navigation Channels at Bahia de Jobos, Aguirre, Puerto Rico, undated (Box 53)
  - Conversion Option for Aguirre Steam Plant Units 1 and 2, 1981 May 28 (Box 53)
  - Submittal by Atlantic Export Corporation (AEC)--Proposal for Services for an Integrated, Captive Coal Supply System and Aguirre Station Conversion, 1982 Oct. 15 (Box 53)
  - A Feasibility Study of the Development of a Deepwater Marine Terminal at or near Aguirre, South Puerto Rico, 1981 Apr. (Box 53)
  - Request for Interpretation of Regulations, 1982 (Box 53)
  - Report Submitted by Blue Ribbon Panel, 1983 Feb. (Box 53)
  - PREPA Response to Draft, 1983 Feb. 18 (Box 53)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel Letters, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
  - PREPA Trip Agenda, 1983 Jan. 18-23 (Box 53)
  - PREPA Trip Notes, 1983 Jan. 11 (Box 53)
  - PREPA--Fuel Cost Data, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
  - System Data Rating and Availability, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel, 1980-1983 (Box 53)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel Material, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
  - Production Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
  - Production Division Monthly Reports, 1982, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - Memorandum on Accounting Procedures and Internal Accounting Controls, 1982 (Box 53)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel Materials, 1982 Nov. and undated (Box 53)
  - Evaluation of the Maintenance Program of PREPA, undated (Box 53)
  - Documentation for Blue Panel Meeting, 1982, Nov. 9, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - PREPA Draft, 1982 Nov. 3 (Box 53)
  - Financial Data, 1981-1982 (Box 54)
  - PREPA Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 54)
  - Economic Regulatory Administration (ERA) 412, 1981 Jun. 30 (Box 54)
  - Corey Correspondence, 1982 (Box 54)
  - Report, 1983 Nov. 3 (Box 54)
  - PREPA Trip Report, 1983 Nov. 1-3 (Box 54)
  - Puerto Rico Materials, 1982 Nov.3 (Box 54)
  - Visit Notes, 1982, Nove. 13-14 (Box 54)
  - Fuels Office Monthly Report, 1982 Oct. (Box 54)
  - PREPA Weekly Generation Report, 1982 Dec. (Box 54)
  - Electricity Generation in Puerto Rico, undated (Box 54)
  - Training Analysis, 1982 Jun (Box 54)
  - Training Recommendations--Executive Summary, 1982 Jul. 1 (Box 54)
  - Maintenance Improvement Program, 1982 Apr. 12 (Box 54)
  - Financial Statements with Auditor's Report, 1981-1982 (Box 54)
  - Survey of Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority Generating Plants, undated (Box 54)
- Pacific Sierra Series, 1949, 1974-1978 and undated
  Consists of state government documents, correspondence, reports, and drafts. Roddis worked as a consultant to the Pacific Sierra Research Corporation. This series consists of reports on topics such as acquifers, solar energy, clean coal power and community heating and cooling systems, and correspondence between Roddis and the company with his comments and suggestions about the reports.
  - Company Brochure, undated (Box 54)
  - Mapping of Geologic Formations and Aquifers of Long Island, New York, 1949 (Box 54)
  - The Transfer of Heat to Peak-Load Periods through an Aquifer Heat Storage System, 1977 Dec. (Box 54)
  - Clean Fuels Derived from Coal--A Critical Development for the Nation, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Capability and Experience in District Healing and Cooling Systems for Communities Through Power Plant Retrofit Distribution Networks, 1978 Mar., 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Robert A. Bell Correspondence, 1978 Apr. (Box 54)
  - Travel Policy for Consultants, 1977 Apr. 1 (Box 54)
  - Jack Lundin Energy Proposal Draft, 1977 Apr. (Box 54)
  - Temperature Distribution in Accumulation of Solar Energy, 1974-1977 (Box 54)
  - A Concept for the Economic Use of Solar Energy in Alaska Using Long-Time Underground Heat Storage, 1977 Jan. 31 (Box 54)
  - Prospects for District Heating in the United States, 1977 Mar.-Apr. (Box 54)
  - Search for Moving Targets, 1976 (Box 54)
  - A National Energy Flow Concept to Remove the Need for Oil Imports, 1977 Jun. 2 (Box 54)
  - An Assessment of Opportunities for Long Term Energy Storage In Aquifers, 1977 Oct. (Box 54)
- Detroit Edison Series, 1972-1987 and undated (bulk 1982-1987)